# YUYOU YU

# www.angelayuyou.com $\label{eq:manchester} Manchester,\,M15~5LA \\ (+44)07800900077 \, \diamondsuit \, y.y.yu@outlook.com$

I started my programming journey by writing small Python script for work and fun. Meanwhile, I built the knowledge of front end HTML and CSS. I found that I was fascinated by programming and started to learn some backend technology and C by myself. There were some difficulties in the learning process so I joined Northcoders' coding bootcamp to start learning systematically. Now I have a good understanding and practice of frontend, backend, data base and network.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Language JavaScript, C, Python

Frontend React, Material-UI, HTML, CSS Backend Express, PostgreSQL, Firebase

Testing Jest, Selenium

Other React Native, Git, Vim

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Northcoders, Manchester

09/2020 - 01/2021

Trainee Software Developer

- · Trained to be a professional software developer in Northcoders' 14 weeks coding bootcamp.
- · Built experiences to work in pairs and groups remotely.
- · Main projects:
  - De-Swap: a React Native Mobile App with real time chatting feature, aim to make fashion more sustainable by allowing people to swap their unwanted clothes.
  - My website: created using React and Material UI.

Go to my website www.angelayuyou.com for more details.

#### Xinlung Group Ltd, Manchester

09/2019 - 06/2020

 $Accommodation \ advisor$ 

- · Self-learned Python to improve work efficiency:
  - Used Python script to download structured data from multiple web pages and converting into Excel format;
- Used Python-Wechat API to send notification messages to certain students automatically.
- · Helped students to find the most suitable accommodation based on individual needs. Provided high level of customer service while achieving the sales targets. Received zero complain. Helped the company to build positive reputation.
- · Built and executed two email marketing campaigns to raise students' awareness on products and sales events(e.g. live stream). 23% of the students booked accommodation with us afterwards.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### the University of Manchester

**BSc.** Fashion Marketing

2016 - 2019

- Achieved 2-2 honor degree
- Worked as financial manager in the final year project of starting a business.
- Grasp multiple software including InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator and Microsoft Office.

the University of Manchester BSc. Management 2015 - 2016

New College Durham BTEC Level 3 2013 - 2015

• Achieved triple grade Distinction\* Distinction\* Distinction

Durham Johnston School GCSE 2008 - 2012

• English: C, Maths: A\*, Additional Maths: B

## **SKILLS**

Language Mandarin(Native), English(fluent)

Software & Tools MS Office, Photoshop, Indesign, Illustrator

## HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Pottery, Board games, Hiking